(Penny:)You went to the dirty store
without me?!
(laughs)
(Leonard:)In sunglasses and a hat after
I parked two blocks away.
Well, get it!
Get it for me!
Yeah?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
Okay, uh, well,
I hope it's fun.
I mean, it-it comes
with paints, and-and
(Leonard:)it's kind of creative
and artistic.
(Penny:)Okay, did you go to
the dirty store or Michaels?
(Emily:)No, no.
(Leonard:)We cover ourselves
in body paint,
and then-then we get on this
big canvas and do our thing.
(Penny:)Whoa, that's kind of
a big step for a guy
(Penny:)who only recently agreed
to take his socks off.
(Leonard:)You're making fun of me.
Forget it.
No! No, come on,
I want to do it.
Really?
(Penny:)Yeah, let's you, me,
(Penny:)and your very, very pale feet
make some art.
(chuckles)
(Penny:)Hey, when you got back to this
store, I want to go with you.
(Leonard:)Okay, but it's a drive-- the
one I went to is in San Diego.
(Howard:)How are the taxes going?
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Bernadette:)But you got a lot of receipts
for the Lego store in here.